If any person gets the Mahadasha of Surya,
then what happens in this direction,
what kind of results does he get,
what things should that
person take care of during the Dasha and what remedies can be there, if
this Dasha is not going very well for you, then in
what way can you help your father-in-law
and develop this mark well,
today we will talk about this,
welcome to one protest from Iran,
our country and yes, when we talk
about the Mahadasha of Surya, then first of all
what is the problem Mahadasha, Surya Mahadasha
means according to the horoscope, Vimshottari Dasha
comes and in Vimshottari Dasha, Mahadasha and
Antardasha occur, the most popular is
Surya Dasha, so we are
talking about the opposite direction, time and the rest of these are the
lights, German industries, there is no
such problem in the horoscope of other directions,
generally people in common parlance are
talking about the Dasha of Surya, that is Vimshottari Dasha, so let
us talk about the Dasha of Surya, that is, Vimshottari Dasha, if any person gets the Mahadasha of Surya, then
what kind of problems can be solved for it.  The results obtained from the Sun are that
one of the most important results obtained is
that the thinking of a person is that he
sneezes a lot, what will happen to you is that if
you are in the direction before this then
it can become loose
and when the
condition of the Sun is with Venus then it does
not mean that you
see things as social work, you
want to do something for your bread, so you
put in doing something like social service which
benefits the mother, which benefits many people,
so here if you do social service at some place,
teaching children, any
social issue, then
social service which gives you a feeling of satisfaction
and he is a beautiful king of the planets,
his work is to
serve the people, so you will
enjoy serving others and you can also add in that way
Surya Gyan, inside the condition of the Sun,
like the light of the Sun is
spread all over the world, there is
sunlight in the entire space, so in the same way
you expand things, if you have a
family going like that and you
enter curious, attachment in the condition of the Sun  Let's take over
this business and you will
expand it and take it to a new level, just like your
father used to do. It is inherited that you will take this
business forward in such a way
that people will be proud of you.
You take any family business that far
under the condition of the Sun. And
if the suit is a little negative, please do
not take the help of your pillar
and you have to forcibly enter that work, then by
drinking your milk,
you must excel in that work, you will
try to take it very far. And if the
Sun is not good in the plate, then you
can also struggle in the same business, there are
chances of this too. So, under the condition of the Sun,
you have to take great care of your health.
You may have to undergo an ID operation, loss of eyesight
or problems related to it,
cataract or any other
diseases can occur under the condition of the Sun.
Therefore, if the Sun is linked to the second and
twelfth house, then it is a very
big property for it and if there is a
connection with the innocent due to this, then it can happen even today
under the condition of your Sun.
You have to take special care of this,
keep your eyes relaxed under the direction of the Sun,
keep your screen time low, in any way
you can,
you have to take special care of this in this condition and when we were
talking about acting roles, then
another factor in it is that while using things, you will
take things towards luxury, you will
start going towards brand,
if you use normal clothes,
you will see branded things,
you will blend things and the tendency of the Sun
increases and if it gets applied then the
chances of it getting even more, so if you have seen
this dress then you can definitely subscribe to this
video
and do videos and
subscribe to the channel and
mix it, then if
you are given a promotion under the condition of the Sun, then there are
chances of you getting a promotion, like you, if an army
soldier is made a bank officer, then such a
vision of the Sun
and you also start leading the group, like a
king, you do not get leadership by looting the public.
Showcasing your skills: If you are in this leading
position, then you will move up in that role
under the condition of the Sun and you will master your role
well. Under this condition,
you will also benefit from the government. So,
if you are in a government job, then there are
more chances of your promotion there.
You get benefits from the government
under the condition of the Sun, that is, it is
possible that if by chance there
is an old question in front of the dormant, this old
employee reference is going on and you can tell the
government how something happened to you, then
you will get success here only in this
direction because these lawyers,
here you have your enemies, the
condition of the Sun also plays a
big role in depositing them, they are very melodious
for any mistake, so your old
cases can be solved by this direction and you have a
lot of chances of getting success. And as
we were talking about social service, if
politics is your career choice, then the
condition of the Sun has a lot of role in politics also.  It plays a
role in taking you to the top most position in
whatever
organization you have or you can become an MLA
of any district or you can become the PM,
so the condition of the Sun plays a big role in
taking you to the top position.
In politics also, the Sun is a revenue planet, it is an
administrative planet, so
where administration or government is concerned, the
Sun is a very important
planet in bringing results to you. The
Sun is the representative of the Sun, the sunlight
representative. If you have been wanting to do any such hobby of yours for a
long time, then you have
not got time, you have
not been able to start it due to some bad breath, then you
must click on it in this condition and
take it forward again, which will give you shoulder
happiness. Chanting a new mantra, becoming a
little religious can also be seen in the condition of the Sun. If you
work to clean the house again, then you can also do it
and if you do not do it then what will you do, now
school is important, it
starts a little before time at home.
Apart from this, you can subscribe for this.
Aditya is the source of heart, that Sun is
yours, so you have to get energy from within it,
and that is that you should do social work
because Sun is the planet itself,
social work and the
work of a king is for people placement, so you should do social
service, serve as many poor people as you
can, you can
wear it after consulting a soldier on your finger, the
owner is not made of lentils and it is
worn on the ring finger of the right hand, the
amount of the world is here, so you
can wear that basic research and you can
also wear the tooth of a pig, so donate things related to Sun, so
now and this
from my channel on the condition of Sun, if you
liked the video, I will update you with new astrological
videos, till then Namaskar